[{"id":1,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585124055360,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":29,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"45","column":"7"},{"id":30,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"46","column":"7"},{"id":31,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"49","column":"7"},{"id":32,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"24","column":"7"},{"id":33,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"25","column":"7"},{"id":34,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"27","column":"7"},{"id":35,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"28","column":"7"},{"id":36,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"29","column":"7"},{"id":37,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"33","column":"7"},{"id":38,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"34","column":"7"},{"id":39,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":40,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":41,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":42,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"62","column":"7"},{"id":43,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"67","column":"7"},{"id":44,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"69","column":"7"},{"id":45,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":46,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":47,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":48,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":49,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":50,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":51,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":52,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":53,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":54,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":55,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":56,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":2,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585123792335,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":29,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"45","column":"7"},{"id":30,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"46","column":"7"},{"id":31,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"49","column":"7"},{"id":32,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"24","column":"7"},{"id":33,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"25","column":"7"},{"id":34,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"27","column":"7"},{"id":35,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"28","column":"7"},{"id":36,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"29","column":"7"},{"id":37,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"33","column":"7"},{"id":38,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"34","column":"7"},{"id":39,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":40,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":41,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":42,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"62","column":"7"},{"id":43,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"67","column":"7"},{"id":44,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"69","column":"7"},{"id":45,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":46,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":47,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":48,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":49,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":50,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":51,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":52,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":53,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":54,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":55,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":56,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":3,"action":"List Page Generation","dateTime":1585123750370,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":29,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"45","column":"7"},{"id":30,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"46","column":"7"},{"id":31,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"49","column":"7"},{"id":32,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"24","column":"7"},{"id":33,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"25","column":"7"},{"id":34,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"27","column":"7"},{"id":35,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"28","column":"7"},{"id":36,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"29","column":"7"},{"id":37,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"33","column":"7"},{"id":38,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"34","column":"7"},{"id":39,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":40,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":41,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":42,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"62","column":"7"},{"id":43,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"67","column":"7"},{"id":44,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"69","column":"7"},{"id":45,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":46,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":47,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":48,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":49,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":50,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":51,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":52,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":53,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":54,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":55,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":56,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":4,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585118441459,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":5,"action":"List Page Generation","dateTime":1585118396522,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":6,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585117998492,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":7,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585117875610,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":8,"action":"Tabs Generation","dateTime":1585117419437,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":9,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585117373725,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":10,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585117259144,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]}]